They don't negotiate with terrorists... they blow them away!
The Delta Force is a action, thriller, adventure film directed by Menahem Golan.
A 707 aircraft jetliner, en route from Athens to Rome and then to New York City, is
hijacked by Lebanese terrorists, who demand that the pilot take them to Beirut.
What the terrorists don't realize is that an elite team of commandos have
been called in to eliminate all terrorists on the jetliner.
Major Scott McCoy, played by Chuck Norris.
Colonel Nick Alexander, played by Lee Marvin.
Ben Kaplan, played by Martin Balsam.
Harry Goldman, played by Joey Bishop.
Abdul, played by Robert Forster.
Sylvia Goldman, played by Lainie Kazan.
The Delta Force is a 1986 American action film starring Chuck Norris and Lee Marvin (in his final film appearance)
as leaders of an elite group of Special Operations Forces personnel based on the real life U.S.
Army Delta Force unit.
Directed, co-written and co-produced by Menahem Golan, the film features Martin Balsam, Joey
Bishop, Robert Vaughn, Steve James, Robert Forster, Shelley Winters and George Kennedy.
It is the first installment in The Delta Force film series.
Two sequels were produced, entitled Delta Force 2: The Colombian Connection
and the direct-to-video Delta Force 3: The Killing Game.
The Delta Force was "inspired" by the hijacking of TWA Flight 847.
The film explores themes of rescue, martial arts, airplane, war veteran, fight.
The tone is intense.